http://www.lindamacdonaldjewellery.com/privacy

Email :
info@lindamacdonaldjewellery.com
/
Telephone :
0
Your basket is empty!
All jewelleryCollectionsThree little birdsInto the WoodsButterfly MoonForeverCherishWee ButtonsWoodlandsMeadowTwilightMoondance EntwinedHearts and FlowersLucky PennyScribblesEnchantedHome is where the heart isSpots & StripesPetiteDaisiesWith LovenewPerfect Christmas Gifts
Home
new
About Linda
Collections
All jewellery
Our Workshop
Home
Privacy Policy
Register Account
If you already have an account with us, please login at the login form.
Your Personal Details
Customer Group
Default
First Name
Last Name
E-Mail
Telephone
Fax
Aruba
Ascension Island (British)
Australia
Austria
Azerbaijan
Bahamas
Bahrain
Bangladesh
Barbados
Belarus
Ethiopia
Falkland Islands (Malvinas)
Faroe Islands
Fiji
Finland
France, Metropolitan
French Guiana
French Polynesia
French Southern Territories
FYROM
Indonesia
Iran (Islamic Republic of)
Iraq
Ireland
Isle of Man
Israel
Italy
Jamaica
Japan
Jersey
St. Helena
St. Martin (French part)
St. Pierre and Miquelon
Sudan
Suriname
Svalbard and Jan Mayen Islands
Swaziland
Sweden
Switzerland
Syrian Arab Republic
Vanuatu
Vatican City State (Holy See)
Venezuela
Viet Nam
Virgin Islands (British)
Virgin Islands (U.S.)
Wallis and Futuna Islands
Western Sahara
Yemen
Zambia
Zimbabwe
Region / State
Your Password
Password
Password Confirm
Newsletter
Subscribe
Yes
No
I have read and agree to the Terms & Conditions
Your Account Has Been Created!
Congratulations! Your new account has been successfully created! You can now take advantage of member privileges to enhance your online shopping experience with us. If you have ANY questions about the operation of this online shop, please e-mail the store owner. A confirmation has been sent to the provided e-mail address. If you have not received it within the hour, please contact us.
Continue
Account Logout
You have been logged off your account. It is now safe to leave the computer.Your basket has been saved, the items inside it will be restored whenever you log back into your account.
Continue
Privacy Policy
Linda Macdonald Jewellery respects your privacy.
Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Linda Macdonald Jewellery.
External Sites.
Linda Macdonald Jewellery is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.
Cookies
A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Linda Macdonald Jewellery to recognize you each time you visit this site(customisation etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Linda Macdonald Jewellery does not use cookies to collect personal information.
What cookies are used on this Website:
The cookies we and our business partners use on this website are broadly grouped into the following categories:Essential – Some of the cookies on our website are essential for us to be able to provide you with a service you have requested. An example of this would be a cookie used to enable you to log into your account on the website or which allows communication between your browser and the website. Our cookie preference cookie described in the section “How can I reject or opt out of receiving cookies?” is also an essential cookie. You may not be able to use our website without these cookies.Analytics – We use analytics cookies to helps us understand how users engage with our website. An example is counting the number of different people coming to our website or using a particular feature, rather than the total number of times the site or feature is used. Without this cookie, if you visited the website once each week for three weeks we would count you as three separate users. We would find it difficult to analyse how well our website was performing and improve it without these cookies.
Social Sharing – We use cookies to allow you to share content directly on the social networking/sharing sites like Facebook, Twitter or Google+. Examples would be if you wanted to “like” or “tweet” about a business or product advertised on our website.
How can I reject or opt out of receiving cookies?
When you first visited this website you will have been shown a message bar drawing your attention to the fact that this website uses cookies and inviting you to review this cookie policy to help manage your cookie preferences. If you do not manage your preferences despite this prompt a cookie preference cookie will be dropped confirming that you consent to us using the cookies detailed in this cookie policy, this cookie preference cookie will last for no more than 5 years.
Please note that we can’t always control third party cookies stored on your machine from our website and where this is the case you will need to visit the relevant third party’s website directly to manage cookies stored on your machine by them. Please see our "Third Party Cookies" section below.
If you want to reject cookies we use from this website you will need to:
delete the cookies from your browser. Most browsers also allow you to prevent all or some cookies being stored on your machine in the future. For more information on how to delete or disable cookies from your browser please use the “help” function within your browser or alternatively visit www.allaboutcookies.org. By deleting our cookie preference cookie the next time you visit this website the cookie message bar will appear again inviting you to again reconsider your preferences; and/or
if you only want to reject the Interest-Based Advertising cookies we store on your machine you can opt-out of receiving these cookies at any time by going to the Internet Advertising Bureau website at http://www.youronlinechoices.com/ and following the opt-out instructions.
Please be aware that disabling cookies may impact the functionality of this website.
Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet
While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Linda Macdonald Jewellery and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Linda Macdonald Jewellery have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.
Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.
free shipping worldwide
Delivery within 3-5 working days
24/7 customer service
Call us 24/7 at +44 (0) 1389 841 848
Product Returns !
Send within 21 days
Location
Laigh Barrs, Main Road, Cardross, G82 5PX
information
hallmarking
about linda
delivery information
privacy notice
newsletter
Copyright © 2020. Linda Macdonald Jewellery Ltd. All Rights ReservedWebsite Design www.elementsdesignstudio.co.uk & dandelion www.dandelionconsultancy.co.uk
